Tom Hoskins collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series IV: Moving Images
  - AFC 2011/026: MV01, March 14, 1965, 1 videocassette (VHS; 11 min., 39 sec.): analog
    - Mississippi John test roll #2 Jacobson Unity
      Hurt walks into a living room in a house, sits down, and picks up a Guild F-30 Sunburst guitar from a case to play. His two grandchildren enter the room one at a time and sit down, followed by his wife Jessie, who also sits down. They listen attentively while he plays. There are close-ups of his hands while he plays, and his granddaughter mimics the action on the chair arm.
    - Mississippi John test roll #3 Jacobson Unity
      Close-up of Hurt's picking style, in slow-motion. Later, Jessie is no longer in the room, and Hurt's granddaughter gets up to dance the twist to Hurt's playing. The video shows Hurt tapping his foot along while playing. His grandson picks up Hurt's hat and hands it to him. Content ends at 8:52; the rest of the video is blank.
  - AFC 2011/026: MV02, 1966, 1 videocassette (VHS; 20 min., 55 sec.): analog
    An edited version of episode 36 of Rainbow Quest (Pete Seeger's television show). "Not the end just the beginning" appears as the title. Also present: Hedy West and Paul Cadwell. Pete engages each in conversation, and they play in turn.
    - Georgia camp meeting
      Performed by Paul Cadwell.
    - You got to walk that lonesome valley
    - Spike driver blues
    - Goodnight, Irene
      Hurt sings lead, and the others play, and join him on the chorus. West leads on the second verse, possibly with Seeger singing harmony.
  - AFC 2011/026: MV03, 1 videocassette (VHS; 1 min., 40 sec.): analog
    Commercial for a car repair company; no content relevant to the collection.
  - AFC 2011/026: MV04, March 14, 1965; 1968; 1980, 1 videocassette (VHS; 60 min.): analog.
    The first two segments are in black and white; the third is in color.
    - Partial copy of the content on MV01, ending on this video
    - An episode of the television show Camera Three ." Son House and Buddy Guy are featured, playing separately and later playing together on the episode.
    - Elizabeth Cotten performing with Mike Seeger, at Ohio University
      This segment is held in copyright by Ohio University.
  - AFC 2011/026: MV05, March 14, 1965, 1 film reel (400 ft.): polyester
    Content is partially copied to MV01. The full content of the film may reflect other content and recording dates.